Thank -- for the meal. (Sword) Thank -- very much.
(Anna) Thank -- very much. please. yes.
The B lunch and set cake will cost 1,000 yen...
that! yes?
--'ve been meaning to say this for a while, but... eh?
Sister, -- beautiful.
Makeup, hairstyle, etc... -- always refer to it!
Ah….
Thank -- for the meal. Ah. --'ll come back later.
thank --.
(humming)
what up?
A girl would be happy if someone told -- -- was beautiful.
It gives -- confidence. Yeah?
Ah, -- hope Tsurugi-san also told --!
-- like -- hair, -- look beautiful, etc.
Tsurugi-san: -- the type who doesn't say unnecessary things.
What -- think about -- sometimes
Even if -- tell -- straight...
eh?
wait a minute.
What do -- have?
Eh, what should -- do? Eh, no...
-- still mentally prepared...
let's go. It's a delivery.
eh?
That's right. It's a request, isn't it? Hehe...
Don't think of strange things.
But was anyone coming?
Before.
Like a week ago?
One year ago.
Hayasaka: -- want this to be delivered to a woman named Mitsuki.
Could -- please check inside?
Oh, of course.
It is nice.
What should -- do about the date and time?
Can -- do that in one year?
Ah...of course.
Well next year
February 24th
At 3pm.
Wear a white coat as a sign
--'ll tell --
There are also requests like that.
A year later, it will be -- first time too.
But why don't -- give it --?
Because this is a proposal, right?
-- wonder what Mitsuki will think when -- give it to --.
-- know this park. It's near -- house.
Really. Yeah.
it is? Yeah. from the client
-- asked -- to buy 33 roses.
Eh... it's no good after all.
-- have to give this to --!
-- can't believe -- going to receive it from Mr. Tsurugi instead.
If it were --, -- would definitely hate it!
--'ll be confused for the rest of -- life!
Nothing to die for!
Ha... And 33 pieces.
It's kind of half-hearted...
Maybe 100 pieces...
Mr. Tsurugi...
--... -- understand.
Yeah?
Mr. Mitsuki.
This is from Mitsuo Hayasaka.
-- came to deliver it on -- behalf.
Ami-chan.
Congratulations.
happy!
thank --!
is that so. Mr. Hayasaka
-- won't come by --
Why not give it --?
A mediocre number of roses. this is
It's a flash mob!
～
Something like 33 pieces.
-- can't convey -- love.
Please marry --.
yes
～
Fufufu… Ahaha….
Ahaha... Mr. Tsurugi
Please don't dance.
It's so interesting that -- decided to watch it.
Hahaha….
(humming)
Mitsuki-san, are -- here yet?
It makes -- all excited.
Mr. Mitsuki. This is from Mitsuo Hayasaka.
-- came to deliver it on -- behalf.
that?
that? It won't start.
What about Mitsuo Hayasaka? that?
(Mitsuki) Mitsuo Hayasaka will not be coming.
Huh? Why? This is a proposal, right?
It's not that they don't come, but that they're here... right?
It's been a while, Courier.
-- was looking forward to meeting --.
What do -- mean?
Mitsuo Hayasaka is
This is -- a year ago.
eh?
It has changed.
Gender too
Even the name.
that's….
-- had surgery.
So this is...
-- gave it to --.
Can -- take it?
yes.
like a dream.
It fits -- well.
-- so glad -- took the plunge
-- think so.
Be the person -- like
Because -- got used to it.
This is the letter and rose that -- kept for --.
It's definitely a confession of love...
It's love for --.
-- thought no one would celebrate.
-- thought -- should at least tell --
-- gave it to --.
Can -- ask -- one more thing?
what do -- want? Preferably on the day
-- would also like -- to send -- a bouquet of flowers.
With 33 roses
Along with the language of flowers
"--'ll still love -- even if -- born again."
Thank -- for delivering it so well.
What happened?
this park
-- remember coming here often with -- mother.
-- haven't seen -- for a while.
-- family wouldn't forgive --.
Sometimes -- think -- should go see --.
But look at it like this
-- understand it painfully.
Those who don't understand
They say they don't understand.
What hurts is
Because it's scary.
Well, someday... -- guess.
That day may never come.
Thank -- so much...
let's go!
eh.
Let -- see what it looks like now.
but….
-- want to meet --, right?
-- should definitely meet.
Why…. Because it's beautiful!
Soooo!
Beautiful Mitsuki
-- should definitely see it.
-- wasn't really surprised.
Did -- know?
The ring -- gave -- is size 16.
It looked like about 18mm. just
It's the size of someone around Hayasaka's size.
Until that point...
Tsurugi-san, -- see too much.
The reason after one year: The meaning of the language of flowers.
Above all, if -- just give it to -- lover
Don't ask --.
That's right.
Now, please sign for receipt.
yes.
Hayasaka: To -- one year from now. How are --.
-- really want to convey -- feelings right now
--'ll send -- this letter.
What do -- think of the ring?
Does it suit --?
-- feel like -- look like --
how is it?
(Hayasaka) What are -- feelings as -- read this?
-- can kind of guess it.
(Hayasaka) It's strange to say it --, but
Congratulations.
-- sure -- have a lot of courage
-- should be able to overcome many trials.
(Hayasaka) -- don't know what anyone will say, but
-- are -- admiration now
-- proud.
Just don't forget that.
Please live -- life with pride.
(Hayasaka) -- who showed courage
from the heart
-- hope -- keep smiling
Ah. please look.
full moon.
It's beautiful.
(Yumi) Shall -- make some coffee?
Mitsuo also drinks...
(Yumi) What's -- name?
-- changed it.
yes.
-- have to take in the laundry...
Shall -- go home soon?
Yeah!
Ah, perfectly round!
It's true. It's a full moon.
-- know, when Mitsuo was born too.
The moon was like that. Is that so?
Therefore, ``Mitsuo''.
A boy as big and dignified as the full moon
-- hope it will be.
If it were a girl, -- wanted -- name to be ``Mizuki.''
Beautiful like a full moon
-- want -- to become a dignified girl.
That's so cute? Yeah. cute!
～
Mitsuki?
eh.
～
Yeah.
Mitsuki...
～
Mitsuki-san, are -- okay?
why --
Were -- thinking of delivering it to -- family?
eh? Because -- thought -- should meet.
--... -- can't think of difficult things like Mr. Tsurugi.
Because that's what -- honestly thought.
Really.
in addition
Isn't it hard?
-- can't see -- family.
here -- are. what? Today is.
Tsukimi omelette curry.
-- made it with the image of a full moon.
Yeah. Hehe….
Mmm, delicious.
Ah.
By the way, -- have a story.
eh.
Eh, eh….
what is it?
Always helpful. -- look forward to -- continued support.
yes? No, sometimes
-- want -- to tell -- straight what -- thinking.
Because -- said it, -- said it.
Mr. Tsurugi
Are -- going to the hospital? -- are open for night emergencies.
Then cancel it. Ah, no, no, no….
-- can't undo it now. -- saved it in -- brain.
Ah.
Even Ken-san couldn't deliver it.
Is there one?
-- was wondering if there was one...
How many times? Oh, -- is like that.
-- just asked!
Really.
Liar.
-- said -- would deliver it...