Thank you for the meal. (Sword) Thank you very much.
(Anna) Thank you very much. please. yes.
The B lunch and set cake will cost 1,000 yen...
that! yes?
I've been meaning to say this for a while, but... eh?
Sister, you're beautiful.
Makeup, hairstyle, etc... I always refer to it!
Ah….
Thank you for the meal. Ah. I'll come back later.
thank you.
(humming)
what up?
A girl would be happy if someone told her she was beautiful.
It gives me confidence. Yeah?
Ah, I hope Tsurugi-san also told me!
I like your hair, you look beautiful, etc.
Tsurugi-san: I'm the type who doesn't say unnecessary things.
What you think about me sometimes
Even if you tell me straight...
eh?
wait a minute.
What do you have?
Eh, what should I do? Eh, no...
I'm still mentally prepared...
let's go. It's a delivery.
eh?
That's right. It's a request, isn't it? Hehe...
Don't think of strange things.
But was anyone coming?
Before.
Like a week ago?
One year ago.
Hayasaka: I want this to be delivered to a woman named Mitsuki.
Could you please check inside?
Oh, of course.
It is nice.
What should we do about the date and time?
Can you do that in one year?
Ah...of course.
Well next year
February 24th
At 3pm.
Wear a white coat as a sign
I'll tell her
There are also requests like that.
A year later, it will be my first time too.
But why don't you give it yourself?
Because this is a proposal, right?
I wonder what Mitsuki will think when we give it to her.
I know this park. It's near my house.
Really. Yeah.
it is? Yeah. from the client
He asked me to buy 33 roses.
Eh... it's no good after all.
I have to give this to you!
I can't believe I'm going to receive it from Mr. Tsurugi instead.
If it were me, I would definitely hate it!
I'll be confused for the rest of my life!
Nothing to die for!
Ha... And 33 pieces.
It's kind of half-hearted...
Maybe 100 pieces...
Mr. Tsurugi...
I... I understand.
Yeah?
Mr. Mitsuki.
This is from Mitsuo Hayasaka.
I came to deliver it on his behalf.
Ami-chan.
Congratulations.
happy!
thank you!
is that so. Mr. Hayasaka
You won't come by yourself
Why not give it yourself?
A mediocre number of roses. this is
It's a flash mob!
～
Something like 33 pieces.
I can't convey my love.
Please marry me.
yes
～
Fufufu… Ahaha….
Ahaha... Mr. Tsurugi
Please don't dance.
It's so interesting that I decided to watch it.
Hahaha….
(humming)
Mitsuki-san, are you here yet?
It makes us all excited.
Mr. Mitsuki. This is from Mitsuo Hayasaka.
I came to deliver it on his behalf.
that?
that? It won't start.
What about Mitsuo Hayasaka? that?
(Mitsuki) Mitsuo Hayasaka will not be coming.
Huh? Why? This is a proposal, right?
It's not that they don't come, but that they're here... right?
It's been a while, Courier.
I was looking forward to meeting you.
What do you mean?
Mitsuo Hayasaka is
This is me a year ago.
eh?
It has changed.
Gender too
Even the name.
that's….
I had surgery.
So this is...
I gave it to myself.
Can I take it?
yes.
like a dream.
It fits you well.
I'm so glad I took the plunge
I think so.
Be the person you like
Because I got used to it.
This is the letter and rose that I kept for you.
It's definitely a confession of love...
It's love for yourself.
I thought no one would celebrate.
I thought I should at least tell myself
I gave it to you.
Can I ask you one more thing?
what do you want? Preferably on the day
I would also like you to send me a bouquet of flowers.
With 33 roses
Along with the language of flowers
"I'll still love you even if I'm born again."
Thank you for delivering it so well.
What happened?
this park
I remember coming here often with my mother.
I haven't seen you for a while.
My family wouldn't forgive me.
Sometimes I think I should go see him.
But look at it like this
I understand it painfully.
Those who don't understand
They say they don't understand.
What hurts is
Because it's scary.
Well, someday... I guess.
That day may never come.
Thank you so much...
let's go!
eh.
Let me see what it looks like now.
but….
I want to meet you, right?
We should definitely meet.
Why…. Because it's beautiful!
Soooo!
Beautiful Mitsuki
You should definitely see it.
I wasn't really surprised.
Did you know?
The ring you gave me is size 16.
It looked like about 18mm. just
It's the size of someone around Hayasaka's size.
Until that point...
Tsurugi-san, I see too much.
The reason after one year: The meaning of the language of flowers.
Above all, if you just give it to your lover
Don't ask us.
That's right.
Now, please sign for receipt.
yes.
Hayasaka: To me one year from now. How are you.
I really want to convey my feelings right now
I'll send you this letter.
What do you think of the ring?
Does it suit you?
I feel like I look like myself
how is it?
(Hayasaka) What are your feelings as you read this?
I can kind of guess it.
(Hayasaka) It's strange to say it myself, but
Congratulations.
I'm sure you have a lot of courage
You should be able to overcome many trials.
(Hayasaka) I don't know what anyone will say, but
You are my admiration now
I'm proud.
Just don't forget that.
Please live your life with pride.
(Hayasaka) You who showed courage
from the heart
I hope you keep smiling
Ah. please look.
full moon.
It's beautiful.
(Yumi) Shall I make some coffee?
Mitsuo also drinks...
(Yumi) What's your name?
I changed it.
yes.
I have to take in the laundry...
Shall we go home soon?
Yeah!
Ah, perfectly round!
It's true. It's a full moon.
You know, when Mitsuo was born too.
The moon was like that. Is that so?
Therefore, ``Mitsuo''.
A boy as big and dignified as the full moon
I hope it will be.
If it were a girl, I wanted her name to be ``Mizuki.''
Beautiful like a full moon
I want you to become a dignified girl.
That's so cute? Yeah. cute!
～
Mitsuki?
eh.
～
Yeah.
Mitsuki...
～
Mitsuki-san, are you okay?
why her
Were you thinking of delivering it to your family?
eh? Because I thought we should meet.
I... I can't think of difficult things like Mr. Tsurugi.
Because that's what I honestly thought.
Really.
in addition
Isn't it hard?
I can't see my family.
here you are. what? Today is.
Tsukimi omelette curry.
I made it with the image of a full moon.
Yeah. Hehe….
Mmm, delicious.
Ah.
By the way, I have a story.
eh.
Eh, eh….
what is it?
Always helpful. I look forward to your continued support.
yes? No, sometimes
I want you to tell me straight what you're thinking.
Because I said it, I said it.
Mr. Tsurugi
Are you going to the hospital? We are open for night emergencies.
Then cancel it. Ah, no, no, no….
I can't undo it now. I saved it in my brain.
Ah.
Even Ken-san couldn't deliver it.
Is there one?
I was wondering if there was one...
How many times? Oh, she is like that.
I just asked!
Really.
Liar.
I said I would deliver it...